ArchotechFireControl
- make it an installable possible quest prize, very high value?
desc: Archotech autonomous weapon control platform is based on a set of principles and technologies
that we cannot comprehend. It may use quantum computing, AI algorithms, and nanotechnology that are
beyond our current understanding. The platform may also be capable of instant communication across
vast distances or even dimensions.
if
<Teok25.ArchotechExpanded>
can build after researching
<ArchotechFireControl>
500 plasteel
1000 gold
1000 silver
15
<Attomachinery>
needs 50kW

CosmicFireControl
desc:The remote control tower designed with Cosmic alloy is an unparalleled feat of technological
advancement. This revolutionary material imbues the tower with extreme durability, heat resistance,
and advanced electromagnetic capabilities. The tower's sleek, metallic exterior is smooth to the
touch and its unique alloy composition is a closely guarded secret.

The tower's advanced capabilities allow it to remotely control weapon emplacements with
unprecedented precision and speed. The tower is fully autonomous, capable of detecting threats and
activating defense mechanisms without any human intervention. Its sophisticated sensors and
computing systems can analyze and process vast amounts of data in real-time, allowing for quick and
accurate responses.

- exists only when
<explodoboy.snsambitioncosmic>
can build after researching
<defName>CosmicFireControl</defName>
<defName>SNS_CosmicAlloy</defName> x 200
<defName>SNS_Component_GenII</defName> x 20
Gold x 300
Silver x 1000
needs 50kW

BasicFireControl
research: BasicFireControl
desc: The simple control panel is designed to operate a few weapon emplacements and is similar to a
drone's control panel. It consists of a compact console with a handful of buttons, switches, and a
joystick. The console is connected to the weapon emplacements via a secure wireless network.

The joystick is used to aim the weapons and adjust their position. The operator can control the tilt
and rotation of each weapon emplacement by moving the joystick in different directions. The buttons
and switches on the console are used to activate the weapons and adjust their firing mode.

The console also features a small screen that displays important data, such as the weapon's status,
ammunition count, and target information. This information is updated in real-time, allowing the
operator to make quick decisions and adjust their strategy as needed.

Overall, the simple control panel is a reliable and efficient way for an operator to control a few
weapon emplacements. Its compact size and intuitive design make it easy to use, while its advanced
features allow for precise control and strategic decision-making.
<costStuffCount>150</costStuffCount>
<costList>
    <Steel>100</Steel>
    <ComponentIndustrial>10</ComponentIndustrial>
</costList>

needs 1kW

AdvancedFire Control
research: AdvancedFireControl
desc: The advanced control panel designed for weapon emplacements has been revolutionized with an
innovative control mechanism: a bowl of goo. The goo is a smart material that can sense and respond
to the operator's touch, allowing for a highly intuitive and flexible control experience.

The bowl of goo is connected to a holographic display that provides a three-dimensional
representation of the weapon emplacements and surrounding area. The operator can touch and
manipulate the goo to control the position and aim of the weapons. For example, by pushing the goo
forward, the operator can adjust the aim of the weapon emplacement to a new location.

The goo is designed with advanced haptic feedback, providing the operator with a realistic sense of
touch and texture. This allows the operator to feel the resistance of the weapon emplacements as
they adjust their position, giving them greater control and precision.

The holographic display also includes a set of advanced features, such as predictive modeling and
real-time data analysis. These features enable the operator to make quick and informed decisions
based on the situation on the ground.
<costList>
    <Steel>400</Steel>
        <Plasteel>50</Plasteel>
        <Gold>50</Gold>
        <ComponentIndustrial>8</ComponentIndustrial>
    ComponentSpacer 1 </costList>

Utlra Fire Control
research: SuperFireControl
The tower's control room is a marvel of engineering, featuring a holographic display that provides
operators with a panoramic view of the surrounding area. The tower's operator can analyze this data
and use it to guide weapon emplacements with remarkable accuracy.
<costList>
    <Plasteel>400
    Silver 500
    <Gold>50</Gold>
    <ComponentSpacer>8
    </ComponentIndustrial>
</costList>